<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Daniel L. Campbell</title>
    <link>https://dxlachlan.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Daniel L. Campbell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 23:36:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dxlachlan.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>桜美林大学ー毎日通学</title>
      <link>https://dxlachlan.github.io/blog/%E6%A1%9C%E7%BE%8E%E6%9E%97%E5%A4%A7%E5%AD%A6%E3%83%BC%E6%AF%8E%E6%97%A5%E9%80%9A%E5%AD%A6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 23:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dxlachlan.github.io/blog/%E6%A1%9C%E7%BE%8E%E6%9E%97%E5%A4%A7%E5%AD%A6%E3%83%BC%E6%AF%8E%E6%97%A5%E9%80%9A%E5%AD%A6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/Ez9J6m5wzQE?autoplay=1&#34; 
  style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this video blog I just put together a small clip to give everyone following a peek into what I see on my daily commute to and from Obirin University. I&#39;ve been putting some thought into more ideas for video blog content, so hopefully these will get a bit more interesting soon.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Week</title>
      <link>https://dxlachlan.github.io/blog/first-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 08:38:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dxlachlan.github.io/blog/first-week/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;center&gt;

&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;../img/fuchinobeStation.jpg&#34; width=&#34;460&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;Fuchinobe Station&lt;/h4&gt;
        
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leaving my Family and Friends behind to move to another country for six months or more was a bit of a difficult decision to make. I had to essentially break away from my daily routine, as well as leave both jobs behind to commit to this program. While I miss my Family and Friends, I&#39;m glad I moved past my hesistance to do this. All of this wouldn&#39;t be completely possible without the Gilman Scholarship Program though, which help me financially make this experience possible.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;center&gt;

&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;../img/obirinScenery.jpg&#34; width=&#34;460&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;Obirin 桜美林大学, Machida-Shi, Tokyo, Japan &lt;/h4&gt;
        
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Landing at Narita I was immediately greeted by Japanese students from Obirin College (桜美林大学). I had been conscious enough to cover all my tattoos just because of cultural differences and the stigma associated with them in Japan. After a substantial amount of other exchange students had arrived they loaded a group of us onto buses which took us to a hotel close to Narita Airport where stayed the first night. That night I was roomed with Chase, an exchange student from Hawaii, who became the first person I met from the Obirin exchange program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;center&gt;

&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;../img/carpeDiemAoyama.jpg&#34; width=&#34;460&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;Carpe Diem BJJ - Aoyama, Tokyo, Japan &lt;/h4&gt;
        
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following day all of the exchange students were wisked onto a bus and immediately driven straight to Obirin (桜美林大学). After our initial orientation, the other students from UNC Charlotte and I were split up as we were all sent to our respective housing situations. After our housing orientation we were free to do whatever we wanted. Knowing I was free to do what I want, I explored downtown Machida that Friday night and visited the Carpe Diem Gym in Aoyama the following morning. 

&lt;br&gt;
&lt;center&gt;

&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;../img/shibuya.jpg&#34; width=&#34;460&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;Downtown Shibuya, Tokyo, Japan&lt;/h4&gt;
        
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;br&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week has been a blur of various orientations getting us prepped for this semester, in addition to two language placement exams. After each day of orientations Sean, Ryan, and I have been exploring various areas around the college and downtown Machida. It&#39;s during each trip out that we&#39;ve been interacting with locals for various reasons forcing us to use our Japanese language skills to varying degrees. From arguing over Izakaya seating charges to asking random girls reptitive questions for no reason other than to talk to them, we&#39;ve been getting decent practice. Today, we finally recieved our results from the placement exams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;center&gt;

&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;../img/donburiMachida.jpg&#34; width=&#34;460&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;h4&gt;Makura Donburi - Machida, Tokyo, Japan&lt;/h4&gt;
        
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was able to place in Level III Japanese Language classes at Obirin which is exactly what I was aiming for. This weekend I&#39;ll be getting registered for class, adjusting my schedule, and running errands before Monday. I also just got the news that my friend Shoya just arrived back in Japan so now I&#39;ll have another friend to hang out with here (´∀｀*).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ニューヨークから町田市に旅行する</title>
      <link>https://dxlachlan.github.io/blog/%E3%83%8B%E3%83%A5%E3%83%BC%E3%83%A8%E3%83%BC%E3%82%AF%E3%81%8B%E3%82%89%E7%94%BA%E7%94%B0%E5%B8%82%E3%81%AB%E6%97%85%E8%A1%8C%E3%81%99%E3%82%8B/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 08:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dxlachlan.github.io/blog/%E3%83%8B%E3%83%A5%E3%83%BC%E3%83%A8%E3%83%BC%E3%82%AF%E3%81%8B%E3%82%89%E7%94%BA%E7%94%B0%E5%B8%82%E3%81%AB%E6%97%85%E8%A1%8C%E3%81%99%E3%82%8B/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/CkC0iKbhz78?autoplay=1&#34; 
  style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my first Video Blog for my Gilman Scholarship. I&#39;ll be updating this site with random content as apart of my Gilman Scholarship follow-on project. Once a week I&#39;ll be uploading a 2 to 5 minute video of highlighting stuff I&#39;ve done or experienced while abroad. This one is just random clips from my travels from Charlotte to New York, to Hong Kong, to Tokyo.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>